Guide to the Jack Shoemaker Papers, 1992-1994
Department of Special Collections
- Series V: Personal Projects and Subject Files
  - Robert Aitken and Brother David Dialogue: draft: May 24, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - American Anthropologist, Oct.-Dec. 1905 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - American Buddhist, May 15, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - The Athena Foundation; prospectus, Aug. 25, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Paul Auster (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Richard Baker, Dharma Sangha (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Basho, Full Moon is Rising (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Joko Beck on Zen (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Benicia Public Library and North Point Press (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - John Berry Lecture at Indiana Farmers Union (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Wendell Berry (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Wendell Berry: essays: "An Argument for Diversity" (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Wendell Berry: "Economy and Pleasure" (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Wendell Berry:"God and Country" (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Wendell Berry: Postscript: Feminism, The Body, The Machine" (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Wendell Berry: "Style and Grace" (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Wendell Berry: "Wallace Stegner and the Great Community" (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Wendell Berry:"Whose Head is the Farmer Using?" (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Wendell Berry:"Why I Am Not Going to Buy a Computer" (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Wendell Berry: "Word and Flesh" (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Wendell Berry:"Writer and Region" (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Wendell Berry: Continuous Clearing (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Wendell Berry: The Wild Birds (2) (Box 18, Folder 25-26)
  - Carl William Bielefeldt, Shobogenzo, Sept,. 1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Robin Blaser, The Violets (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Gus Blaisdell, Abstracts of Intimacy (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Gus Blaisdell: One Made It (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Gus Blaisdell: Prose Ocean (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Gus Blaisdell: Skeptical Landscapes (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Murray Bookchin, anarchism pamphlets (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Harry Braun, "The Politics of Zen," Fall 1961 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Chinese grammar and pronunciation (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Ling Chung, The Cold Mountain, U. Wisc. M.A. thesis, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Kenneth Cohen, "Water Wisdom in Chinese Poetry" (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Peter Coyote (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - J.C. Cleary, A Tune Beyond the Clouds (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Thomas Cleary (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Francis Cook, "Hua-Yen and Process" (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - John Daniel (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - "The Darkness of God" (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Richard Dauenhauer, Erotic Epigrams (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Guy Davenport, correspondence (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Guy Davenport: articles (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Barry Eisenberg, The First Green: Poems, draft 1 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Barry Eisenberg, The First Green: Poems: draft 2 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Mircea Eliade, "Memory and Forgetting" reprint (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Ross Feld (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Richard Felger, "Down in the Fog Desert" (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Rick Fields, "Alarm Clock Buddha" (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - M.F.K. Fisher (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Doug Foster (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Paula Fox (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - G.S. Frazer. "Japanese Poetics" (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Lucien Freud (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Dominique Gioia (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - James Heap: offprints (2) (Box 20, Folder 12-13)
  - Peter Howard and ABAA Ethics Commission (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Huichol Art (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Bev Jafek (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Ann Jauregin (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Hans Jenny, "The Image of Soil in Landscape..." (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Jess (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Ronald Johnson (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Ronald Johnson: Ark, 34-50 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Ronald Johnson: Ark, 52-62 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Ronald Johnson: Ark, 70-78 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Ronald Johnson: reviews (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Kawabata, Watch With Me: Stories (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
  - Ed Kleinschmidt (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Anne Lamott (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Barry Lopez (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Michael McClure: misc. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Michael McClure: The Daily Vision (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Michael McClure: Fields (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Michael McClure: Fragments of Desire (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Michael McClure: Listen, Lawrence (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Michael McClure: "Peyote" (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Michael McClure: September Blackberries (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Michael McClure: Xes (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Michael McClure: We (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Scott McLean (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Tom and Ginny Marsh (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Abe Masao, Dogen reprint from The American Buddhist (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Russell Means, "Fighting Words" from Mother Jones (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - W.S. Merwin (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Chuck Miller (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Mozart: Kochel listing (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Gary Nabhan (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Benjamin Olson, Tao Te Ching (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Ezra Pound: miscellaneous clippings (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Will Powers, "Designing Literature" reprint (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Reynolds Price: correspondence (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Reynolds Price: interviews and reprints (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - "Reinventing Nature" conference at U. California, Santa Cruz, Feb. 9. 1993: notes (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Susan Roether, "Reflections on Color": reprint (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Ned Rorem (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Oliver Sachs (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - James Salter (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Steve Sanfield, miscellaneous (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Steve Sanfield: "High John the Conqueror" (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Steve Sanfield: Snyder Memoir (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Steve Sanfield: "We Are Not Alone" (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Ed Snow, "Bruegelian Assurance": photocopy (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Gary Snyder: business: archive and book orders (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Gary Snyder: correspondence nd; 1987-1989 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Gary Snyder: correspondence 1990-1993 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Gary Snyder: drafts: The Practice of the Wild introduction, "The Poetics of Emptiness", Earth Day statement (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Gary Snyder: Hippies from Old Japan (TMs) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Gary Snyder:"On Common Ground" conference materials (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Gary Snyder: "Raven's Beak River" (TMsS) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Gary Snyder: Shoemaker proposal for critical anthology (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Gary Snyder: syllabi, conservation studies classes (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Gary Snyder: concerning John Yau's review of American Poetry Since 1950 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Kai Snyder, Action Packet: A Directory for Environmental Action (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Kai Snyder: correspondence (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Sutra of Healing (reprint) (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Beatrice Suzuki, Mahayana Buddhism (reprint) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Robert Sund, Easter greeting to North Point staff (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Kazuaki Tanahashi, "One Stroke" exhibit pamphlet (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Norman Waddell, Hakuin (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Leslie Whitten re William D. Turnbull article (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Geoff Young (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Series VI: Unpublished Manuscripts
  - Steven Barclay, Writers Talk (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Murray Bookchin, Ethics for an Ecological Society (4 folders) (Box 23, Folder 17-20)
  - Bernard Cooper, Maps to Anywhere (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Albert Dalia, The Cry of the Gibbon (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Lars Eigner, Travels with Lizbeth (Box 24, Folder 3-6)
  - Peter Haskel, Before Your Eyes: an Introduction to the Zen of Sokei-An (Box 24, Folder 7-12)
  - Peter Haskel, Before Your Eyes: Introduction (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Peter Haskel, Before Your Eyes: North Point contracts and background (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Peter Haskel, Before Your Eyes: Pantheon proposal and background (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Ibuse Masuji: Stories (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Laura [Riding] Jackson: correspondence about reissuing her work, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Laura [Riding] Jackson: misc. projects (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Laura [Riding] Jackson: Rational Meaning (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Paul Jaffe, Flowers Fall (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Ron Johnson, Collected Poems (Box 25, Folder 5-10)
  - Laura Kasischke, Suspicious River (Box 25, Folder 11-14)
  - Petra Kelly, Thinking Green (Box 25, Folder 15-18)
  - Sidney Lea, On the Lookout: Notes from a Life Outside (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
  - Taigen Dan Leighton, Bendowa: Talk on Wholehearted Practice (Box 26, Folder 4-6)
  - A.J. Liebling, Liebling At the New Yorker: background (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - A.J. Liebling, Liebling At the New Yorker: correspondence (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - A.J. Liebling, Liebling At the New Yorker: p & l (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Bonnie Mc Dougall, Bei Dao (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Carole Maso, The American Woman in the Chinese Hat (Box 26, Folder 11-14)
  - Carole Maso, The American Woman in the Chinese Hat: correspondence (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Carole Maso, The American Woman in the Chinese Hat: editorial (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Frances Mayes, One Hundred Angels (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Margaretta Mitchell, Dance for Life (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Morinaga Soko Roshi, No Birth, No Death (4) (Box 27, Folder 3-6)
  - Morinaga Soko Roshi, No Birth, No Death: author questionnaire (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Morinaga Soko Roshi, No Birth, No Death: contracts and p & l (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Morinaga Soko Roshi, No Birth, No Death: editorial (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Gary Nabhan, Desert Follies (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Bill Porter, Road to Heaven: art (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Bill Porter, Road to Heaven: author questionnaire (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Bill Porter, Road to Heaven: contracts (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Bill Porter, Road to Heaven: drafts (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Bill Porter, Road to Heaven: editorial (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Barbara Roether, At a Certain Speed (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Steve Sanfield, American Zen (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Steve Sanfield, American Zen Hopes and Reports (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Leslie Scalapino, Defoe (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
  - Mike Twohy, legal cartoons (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Luisa Valenzuela, Erotic Stories by Latin American Women (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Peter Whigham, A Dante Portfolio (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Koun Yamada, Fresh Face of Zen (3) (Box 28, Folder 6-8)
  - Minoru Yoshioka, Kusudama (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Series VII: Pantheon Manuscripts
  - Robert Aitken, Encouraging Words: from box marked "early draft" (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
  - Robert Aitken, Encouraging Words: Ms marked "house copy; updated 8/20" with editor's tags (Box 29, Folder 3-7)
  - Robert Aitken, Encouraging Words: setting manuscript with layout instructions (Box 29, Folder 8-13)
  - Robert Aitken, Encouraging Words: typeset photocopy with corrections (Box 30, Folder 1-5)
  - Robert Aitken, Encouraging Words: emendations and notes for paperback edition, Robert Aitken, Encouraging Words: paste up: sample pages (os) (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Robert Aitken, The Practice of Perfection: bound draft with letter dated 10/1/92 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Robert Aitken, The Practice of Perfection: disk copy dated Feb. 24, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 8-11)
  - Robert Aitken, The Practice of Perfection: bound, uncorrected galleys, Robert Aitken, The Practice of Perfection: paste up sample pages and cover (os) (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Wendell Berry, Entries: draft marked "unedited gathering 9-15-92, not for circulation" with JS notes (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Wendell Berry, Entries: setting manuscript, dated Aug, 26, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Wendell Berry, Entries: typeset photocopy (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Wendell Berry, Entries: bound, uncorrected galleys (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Wendell Berry, Entries: paste up sample pages and cover photo (os)
  - Wendell Berry, Fidelity: early drafts, "Are You All Right?" (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Wendell Berry, Fidelity: early drafts, "Fidelity" (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Wendell Berry, Fidelity: "A Jonquil for Mary Penn" (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Wendell Berry, Fidelity: "Making it Home" (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Wendell Berry, Fidelity: "Pray Without Ceasing" (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Wendell Berry, Fidelity: setting manuscript, nd (Box 31, Folder 9-12)
  - Wendell Berry, Fidelity: version marked "master pages", Jun. 24, 1992, Wendell Berry, Fidelity: cover design (os) (Box 31, Folder 13-16)
  - Wendell Berry, Sex, Economy, Freedom & Community: early drafts, "A Bad, Big Idea" (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Wendell Berry, Sex, Economy, Freedom & Community: drafts, "Christianity and the Survival of Creation" (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Wendell Berry, Sex, Economy, Freedom & Community: drafts, "Conservation is Good Work" (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Wendell Berry, Sex, Economy, Freedom & Community: drafts, "Conservation and Local Economy" (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Wendell Berry, Sex, Economy, Freedom & Community: drafts, "Out of Your Car" (reprint) (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Wendell Berry, Sex, Economy, Freedom & Community: drafts, "Peaceableness Toward Enemies" (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Wendell Berry, Sex, Economy, Freedom & Community: drafts, "The Problem of Tobacco" (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Wendell Berry, Sex, Economy, Freedom & Community: draft, "Sex, Economy, Freedom & Community" (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Wendell Berry, Sex, Economy, Freedom & Community: introduction, dedication and corrections (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Wendell Berry, Sex, Economy, Freedom & Community: typeset photocopy, with corrections (Box 32, Folder 10-13)
  - Wendell Berry, Sex, Economy, Freedom & Community: uncorrected bound galleys (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Wendell Berry, Watch With Me (form'ly How They Did) draft: "the Lost Bet" (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Wendell Berry, Watch With Me (form'ly How They Did) draft: "Turn Back the Bed" (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Wendell Berry, Watch With Me (form'ly How They Did) draft: "Watch With Me" (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Wendell Berry, Watch With Me (form'ly How They Did) draft: Watch With Me: full draft Ms, with corrections (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
  - Wendell Berry, Watch With Me (form'ly How They Did) draft: typeset photocopy, with corrections (Box 33, Folder 4-6)
  - Wendell Berry, Watch With Me (form'ly How They Did) draft: bound, uncorrected galleys (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Wendell Berry, Watch With Me (form'ly How They Did) draft: layout (os)
  - Wendell Berry, Watch With Me (form'ly How They Did) draft: cover portrait (os)
  - John Daniel, The Trail Home: full draft, with corrections (3) (Box 33, Folder 8-10)
  - John Daniel, The Trail Home: setting manuscript, with corrections (3) (Box 33, Folder 11-14)
  - John Daniel, The Trail Home: paperback edition: addenda: "Wallace Stegner" and "The Limits of Paradise" (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - John Daniel, The Trail Home: corrections and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - John Daniel, The Trail Home: photocopied galleys, John Daniel, The Trail Home: layout (os 2); Guy Davenport, The Geography of the Imagination: cover design (os 2) (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, Stay Me, Oh Comfort Me: draft marked "original unedited" (Box 34, Folder 1-8)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, Stay Me, Oh Comfort Me: from Ms marked "Fisher: cut material" (Box 34, Folder 9-12)
  - Fisher, Stay Me: cut material (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
  - Fisher, Stay Me: Norah's introduction, with note (Feb. 12, 1993) (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Fisher, Stay Me: galley photocopies, with corrections (Box 35, Folder 4-9)
  - Fisher, Stay Me: additional corrected pages, with flags (July 2, 1993), Fisher, Stay Me: page design (os 2) (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, full draft Ms, To Begin Again (form'ly Legend of Love) (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, full draft Ms, To Begin Again (form'ly Legend of Love): To Begin Again: material cut from original Ms (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, full draft Ms, To Begin Again (form'ly Legend of Love): corrected Ms, with flags (Box 36, Folder 1-4)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, full draft Ms, To Begin Again (form'ly Legend of Love): copyedited house copy (Box 36, Folder 5-8)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, full draft Ms, To Begin Again (form'ly Legend of Love): setting Ms (Box 36, Folder 9-13)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "About Looking Alone at a Place" (TMs with AN) (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "An Alphabet for Gourmets" reprint (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"The Ancients Among the Lettuces" (TMs reprint) (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"Announcement from Israfel" (TMs; multiple drafts (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"An American Legend" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"Another Love Story" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"Answer in the Affirmative" (TMs reprint, with AN) (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"Bad Manners: A Comedy in Three Acts" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"A Ballad" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"The Best Meal I Ever Ate" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"The Black Pest" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"A Clown Unknown But Recognized" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"A Communication" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Consider the End" (TMs with AN, reprint) (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"Culinary Compassion"(TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"A Cure Performed by the Professor" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "A Curious Vernacular" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"The Day for Innocence" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"A Delayed Meeting" (reprint) (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"Diplomatic, Retired" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Direct Approach" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"Eesh-Tam-Bool" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"End of the Silent Winter"(TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"Epatant!" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing:"The Exploits of Anne Philippe" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Family Theater"(TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "A Few of the Men" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Fingers Were Made Before..." (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Gastronomical Snobs" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Gin and Bitters" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Good Food Out Here" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Grave Taste" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Green Talk" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Hair of the Dog" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "HBD: Colored Wine Glasses" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "HBD: Nectarine Punch" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "HBD: Sherry Glasses" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Henriette" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Honest is Good" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "How to Cast a Spell" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "How to Catch a Sea Monster" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "How to Cook A Coon" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "How to Die Gracefully" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "How to Prove a Theory" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "In Honorable Combat" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "If I Were Running This Place" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Importance of Nothing Much" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "An Interview with Mr. Amos Sterne" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "A Kiddle Edye Vedoo" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "A Kitchen Allegory" (reprint) (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Last House" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Legend" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "To Look and Wonder" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Lost, Strayed, Stolen" (reprint) (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Mahogany Tree" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Magic Eye of the Idol of Osiris" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Maidie (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Martini-Zheen, Anyone?" (reprint) (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Mess Call" (TMs reprint) (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Minutes of the Last Meeting" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Motivation, Raison d'Etre..." (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Mr. Wentworth's Party" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Mrs. Fisher's Infamous Five-Day Diet" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Mrs. Teeters' Tomato Jar" (reprint) (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Murder at Lilac Cottage" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Night in a French Town" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "A Note on the Social Hazards...of Amateur Cooking" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Notes on a Necessary Pact" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Notes on the Craft...of Missing" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "O Cuckoo!" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Obit for Charles Sommerville" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Obvious" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Ode to the Olive" (reprint) (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Old Woman" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Oldest Man" (reprint) (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "One of Many Reasons" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Pacific Village" (reprint) (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Possible: A Kind of Elegy" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Post War Proposition" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Private War in Provence" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "A Question Answered" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "A Rain Song" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 23)